<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Subtrakt</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://wwww.subtrakt.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://wwww.subtrakt.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 21:31:35 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 21:31:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Subtrakt: A New Name</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt; It’s official! I&#39;ve changed Visualty.io to Subtrakt.io. So why did I decide to change the name of my website when I thought I had chosen a clever and strategic name? Simply put, Subtrakt is easier to spell and remember!

&lt;p&gt; We all know how difficult it is to come up with a creative, memorable name that captures everything we stand for, and I’d like to think that Subtrakt does just that. I like what it means: it represents the operation of removing objects from a collection. But instead, I like to think of it as a metaphor for good design. &quot;Less is more&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s to launching the name of my website, Subtrakt. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://wwww.subtrakt.io/blog/2016/05/31/new-name.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wwww.subtrakt.io/blog/2016/05/31/new-name.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;New year, new website!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Wow! What a year it&#39;s been! Lots of exciting changes in 2015. I left my full-time job at Apple to launch my own &lt;a href=&quot;http://wwww.subtrakt.io&quot;&gt;freelance business&lt;/a&gt;, visited Southeast Asia for the first time, got engaged to my best friend (while also helping her start her own business &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altbrides.com&quot;&gt;Alt. Brides&lt;/a&gt;) and finally built my well-overdue portfolio website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve learned a lot in the past year, mainly, what it means to be happy and to constantly challenge myself. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What is happiness?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coffee, pizza and beer? Well, that&#39;s just part of what it means to be happy. To me happiness is having creative freedom over every design challenge I take on. Happiness also comes from being trusted by my clients to drive design forward and make apps better. This is what I truly love and value about being a &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@ericeriksson/what-is-product-design-9709572cb3ff#.qlutcfvrm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Product Designer&lt;/a&gt;. Being an integral part of helping companies improve their products by interweaving design-thinking into the software development process.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Just the beginning&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I have ambitious plans to work hard (and smart), innovate, have fun in the process and find the right talent to help me succeed.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just the beginning folks. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://wwww.subtrakt.io/blog/2016/01/06/hello-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wwww.subtrakt.io/blog/2016/01/06/hello-world.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
